Cold as Hell
100 Degrees Below Zero is a action, science fiction
film directed by Richard Schenkman.
After freak climate and weather events destroy the world around them, a group
of rogue scientists attempt to reverse the deadly new ice age.
Ralph Dillard, played by John Rhys-Davies.
Steve, played by Jeff Fahey.
Lacey, played by Judit Fekete.
Jackson, played by Andray Johnson.
Taryn, played by Sara Malakul Lane.
Jana Foster, played by Jane Doole.
This is an alphabetical list of film articles (or
sections within articles about films).
It includes made for television films.
See the talk page for the method of indexing used.
It covers film titles that begin with a number, whether
written in Arabic numerals or spelled out.
Excluding articles (e.g., "a", "an", "the" in English), it does not
include film titles containing numbers after the first word.
The film explores themes of escape, volcano, iceland, europe, frozen alive.
The tone is thought_provoking.